# Blake Stefansen

### Contact

Address

Gainesville, FL, 32607

E-mail

bstefansen11@gmail.com

WWW

https://bstefansen.github.io

/Portfolio

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com

/in/blake-stefansen/

## Skills

JavaScript

Geographic Information

Systems (GIS)

React.js

Node.js

MongoDB

WordPress

Express.js

**Adobe Suite** 

**Google Analytics** 

Python

**SQL** 

GraphQL

Azure

University of Florida Honors | Geoscience Graduate with a passion for technology and the natural world. I specialize in JavaScript and have trained with GIS products, Python, SQL, MongoDB, React, Node, Express.js, GraphQL, HTML, CSS, Git/Github, WordPress, Microsoft Office, Google Suite, Google Analytics, and Adobe Suite. I have a strong foundation in software and web development, graphic design, geographic information systems analysis, and the geological sciences.

Take a look at my portfolio, and let's get in touch! https://bstefansen.github.io/Portfolio/

## Work History

2020-05 -

#### Founder

Current

Get Sufficient

- Founded Get Sufficient: an online media WordPress blog about self-sufficiency and sustainability.
- Configured domain, hosting, Google Analytics, and back-end security.
- Deployed custom CSS and HTML.
- Customized and configured diverse plugins and themes.

2019-05 -

## Associate Field Geologist

2019-06

TERRA-COM Environmental Consulting, Inc.

- Collaborated with geologists in preparation of site assessments.
- Executed groundwater sampling field services compliant with FDEP regulations.

2016-01 -

#### Office Assistant

2019-04

Florida Credit Union

- Launched first annual cost analysis report of office supplies, informing senior management on optimizing annual savings.
- Developed and managed ordering systems and databases for company supplies through Smartsheet and Excel, streamlining ordering procedures for company branches and departments.
- Reduced vendor pricing of office supplies and supervised inventory of corporate office, saving \$2000 annually.
- Drafted and optimized procedures for diverse office

tasks.

2015-10 -	Customer Service Representative
2015-12	Walgreens
	<ul> <li>Managed the front register and interacted with</li> </ul>

- customers.
- Maintained receipts and answered incoming phone requests.
- Gave appropriate change, requested price checks, and rung up sales.

## Certifications

2019-05	40-Hour OSHA HAZWOPER Online   Safety Unlimited, Inc.
2020-04	MERN // Full Stack   freeCodeCamp.org
2020-05	Geospatial Information Analysis   University of Florida
2020-07	Microsoft Certified: Azure Fundamentals

## Education

2018-05 -	Cum Laude   Bachelor's Degree:
2020-05	Geological and Earth
	Sciences/Geosciences
	University of Florida
2017-05 - 2018-05	Associate of Arts: Geology
	Santa Fe College

# **Additional Information**

#### Honors & Awards:

- Cum Laude | Honors University of Florida May 2020
- Honors Graduate Santa Fe College 2018
- Charles L. Blount Scholarship Santa Fe College 2017
- Florida Bright Futures Scholarship FDOE 2017
- Florida Credit Union Scholarship FLCU 2017
- Education Foundation Senior Scholarship ACPS 2017